If we connected our hearts together
ハ — トをつなげたら
Earth would be a glittering, shining planet
キラキラ輝く地球
These dreaming feelings are
夢見るこの想いは
shining pieces of a bigger puzzle
輝くパズルの piece
When I slowly came down the stairs
眠い目をこすりながら
rubbing my sleepy eyes,
ゆっくり階段を降りたら
I was in an unknown place
見知らぬ場所
There was a distinguished-looking rabbit hopping about
うさぎの紳士が跳ね回る
There’s a door that emerges into a rainbow
虹に浮かび上がるドア
and bubble gum that gives you dreams
夢を見せる バブル・ガム
Let’s put on our glass slippers and set out
ガラスの靴を履いて出掛けよう
If we believe that the images in our head can become reality
イメ — ジは実現すると信じたら
they’ll come true with just a wink!
叶うの ウィンク！  するだけで
It moved me to tears, the color of the sky
泣き出した 空の色
is always nearby, no matter the time
いつだって そばにある
No matter where you are, the same moon floats above us
どこにいたって同じ
in the creamy sky
月が浮かぶ creamy sky
Lying down on top of the marshmallow clouds,
マシュマロの雲の上
I looked down below
寝転んで見降ろした
This world is so fun!
この世界は so fun
A sparkling Earth of Hearts
きらめく ハ — トの地球
Whenever an anxious-to-please clown
ご機嫌取りのピエロが
comes closer, I think
近づいてくるたび思うの
I’m not a child!
こどもじゃない
Cut it out! Take care in how you handle me
やめて 取り扱いに注意
When do full-fledged, proper ladies cry?
一人前のレディは
I’ll sing about my dreams by the lakeside
湖のほとりで夢を歌う
I don’t particularly want you to make me laugh
別に笑わせて欲しいわけじゃないわ
I’d rather you please watch gently over me
お願い 優しく 見守って
It’s a promise
約束よ 離れたら
If we’re separated, you might lose heart but
心細くなるけど
don’t despair
悲しみに暮れないで
because I’ll be cheering for you
応援してるから
When I open the music box
宝物を集めた
where I collected all my treasures,
オルゴ — ルを開いて
They’re bonds between us that have been tested and confirmed
確かめた絆
An Earth made of everyone’s hearts
みんなの ハ — トの地球
If we connected our hearts together
ハ — トをつなげたら
Earth would be a glittering, shining planet
キラキラ輝く地球
These dreaming feelings are
夢見るこの想いは
shining pieces of a bigger puzzle
輝くパズルの piece
I’ll show you I can protect you
願い事を食べてしまう
from those mean old monsters
イジワルな monsters
that swallow up dreams!
守ってみせるよ
Don’t let anyone trick you
誰にも惑わされないで
Let’s go on a fun journey full of adventure
楽しい 冒険の旅をしよう
It’ll be okay, close your eyes
大丈夫 目を閉じて
I'll always be here
いつだって ここにある
Even if we’re far apart, the same dream
離れていても 同じ
floats above us in the creamy sky
夢が浮かぶ creamy sky
It moved me to tears, the color of the sky
泣き出した 空の色
is always nearby, no matter the time
いつだって そばにある
No matter where you are, the same moon floats above us
どこにいたって 同じ
in the creamy sky
月が浮かぶ creamy sky
Lying down on top of the marshmallow clouds,
マシュマロの雲の上
I looked down below
寝転んで見降ろした
This world is so fun!
この世界は so fun
A sparkling Earth of Hearts
きらめく夢 ハ — トの地球